<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_width="320dp"
    android:minHeight="250dp"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content">

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scroll"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_weight="1">
        <LinearLayout
            android:orientation="vertical"
            android:background="@color/colorLightBlue"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试"
                />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/content"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试测试"
                />

        </LinearLayout>

    </ScrollView>

    <LinearLayout
        android:id="@+id/bottom"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="50dp">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/cancel"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="取消"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/confirm"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="确定"/>

    </LinearLayout>

</LinearLayout>